（雷鳴）
（コン　コン）
（大魔王）うんたた　うんた…→
ぎゃあああ！
またやっちゃった～→
I screwed up again!
ど～うしても
ここのリズムがとれん～。→
I just can't get this rhythm here right!
うんたた　うんた
は～るさめがすき…なんだよな～。
I lo~ve noodles! Or something like that...
あ　そうだ！人間界　もう夏休み？
Oh, that's right! Is it summer
vacation in the Human World?
俺の息子にさ　夏休みの宿題
送っといて。
That son of mine... Send him
some summer homework, would ya?
（側近）はて？宿題ですか？
Um, homework?
（大魔王）うん　夏休みっていえば
宿題でしょう。→
Yeah! I mean, summer vacation
always comes with homework, right?
一通り　何となく
フルセットで。じゃ　お願いね。
One of those, full-set thingamajigs...
Anyway, make it so!
うんたた　うんた
も～どりがつおに　うんた…。
（ヒルダ）…と　いうことだ。
And there you have it.
（ベル坊）ア～イ　ダ～ブ～。
（男鹿）なにが　と　いうことだ！
なんだこりゃ！？
And there you have what, exactly?
What the hell?
夏休みの宿題だ。
Summer vacation homework.
こいつは乳児だろ！？
乳幼児に　宿題はねぇ！
He's an infant!
Infants don't have homework!
大魔王様からのありがたい宿題だ。
You should be thankful for this
homework sent by the Great Demon Lord.
お前のような　ドブ男ごときが→
Most gutter trash would never
set eyes on a bounty like this.
本来　一生
目にすることもできない。
伏して拝め。
うるせえ！今すぐ送り返せ！
Get down and kneel before it.
Shut up! Send it back this instant!
アランドロン呼んできて
腹ん中つっこめ～！
Call Alaindelon and stuff it in his stomach!
やれやれ
これだから　下等な人間は…。
What am I to do with you?
You are such a vulgar boor.
夏休みの標本にすっぞ　コラ！
You want me to pin you up as
a summer vacation sample, eh?
もう無理だ。
あん？
It's too late.
坊っちゃまが　お開けになられた。
The master has unsealed the wrapping.
ダブ～ッ。
ノオーッ！！
待て！こら　ベル坊！
ア～イ～！
Wait a sec, Baby Beel!
だから　もう遅いと
言っておるだろう。
See, I told you. It's already too late.
うむ　開封すると梱包材が自然に
なくなる。エコだ。
Yes... When opened, the
wrapping naturally disappears.
過剰包装だろうが！
Environmentally friendly.
There's way too much packaging!
おお　これは魔界絵日記か。
This is a Demon picture diary!
魔界朝顔栽培セットに→
A Demon morning-glory planting kit...
魔界採集キットもあるな。
And a Demon gathering kit, too.
さすが大魔王様。
坊っちゃまのことを　こんなにも。
As expected from the Great Demon Lord...
He thinks so much of the master!
いやいや　ヒルダさん
ぜんぜんまったく　これっぽっちも→
Um, no, Hilda-san. I have not the tiniest,
slightest intention of accepting this.
受け取る気はないんで
早々に送り返していただけますか。
So might you send it back without delay?
何を言っている　ほら見ろ→
What are you spouting?
坊っちゃまのお名前が
このように。
Look at how the master's name is written...
Kaiser de Emperana Beelzebub IV
うわぁ　久々に見たな。フルネーム。
Haven't seen the full name in a while...
って　名前書いてあろうが
何だろうが関係ねえ！
Anyway, it doesn't matter if his
name or whatever is written on it!
アランドロンの…早っ！
Call Alaindelon...
（アランドロン）男鹿殿。至急ということ
でしたので→
That was fast!
Oga-dono... As you requested great
haste, I have used a smidgen of force.
いささか乱暴ではございましたが
古市殿をお連れいたしましたぞ。
I have brought Furuichi-dono with me!
古市は呼んでねえ！（古市）呼ばれてすらいねえ～！
I didn't call for Furuichi!
He didn't even call me!
うう～っ　俺の高原物語～…→
My epic highlands tale!
前回　誰かさんのせいで
俺の海物語を邪魔されたじゃない？
Thanks to someone, my epic beach
tale was ruined, remember?
だから　今度こそと思って
家族で高原にでかけたの！→
So I thought, "this time!" and went
to the highlands with my family!
なのに…こ　これが…！イェ～イ！
And yet... This!
Yay.
((どこから来たんですか？))
Where did you come from?
((くぅ～…あっ！))
（男鹿の声）((アランドロン呼んできて
腹ん中つっこめ！))
Call Alaindelon and stuff it in his stomach!
((シュタ！))
（古市）((よかったら…アア～！))
In that case...
責任とってよ～！ねぇ　責任～！
Take responsibility!
Take it, okay?
（古市の泣き声）
ギャウギャウ…。
うう…いいかげんにしろ！
Cut it out!
グッ　ううう…。
昔々　あるところに
それはそれは凶悪で　残忍で→
Once upon a time, in a land far far away...
there was a barbaric, ruthless, defiant,
傍若無人で　人を人とも思わぬ→
demon-like bastard who thought
nothing of his fellow man.
悪魔のような男がおりました。
…って　おい！？
Hey!
How About Some Demon World Homework?
きゃ～　重い。私　無理
男鹿殿　ギブです。
So heavy!
I can't handle it! Oga-dono, I give in!
ちょっともう　無理だって…→
I said I can't take it!
宛名を…宛名を書いて
下さらないと！
Unless you write... Unless you
write who it's addressed to...
魔界行き　大魔王宛だ！この野郎！
Send it to that Great Demon Lord
in the Demon World, you bastard!
無茶でございます！
You're pushing it too far!
でも　そんな強引な
男鹿殿も　ス・キ…ぽ！
But... I like how you
can get rough with me...
ううう…だあぁ～！
うるせえ！えい！
Shut up!
いい加減にしろ。
Enough of this.
You think I'm just gonna
let this be dumped on me?
こんなもん　一方的に
押し付けられて　たまるかよ！
貴様は　宿題というものが
全く理解できていないようだな。
I do not think you comprehend
what "homework" really is.
自慢じゃねえが　生まれてこの方
宿題をやったことは→
Not to brag, but I have never done
homework once in my entire life!
一度もねえ！
本当に自慢じゃねえ。
It's not something to brag about.
よいか　魔界の宿題とは
己を限界まで高め→
Listen carefully. This is
what Demon World homework is:
Work that will challenge your very limits,
魂の最後の一滴まで搾り出すもの
そこにあるのは食うか食われるか。
and squeeze out every last drop of your life!
With homework, it's eat or be eaten!
弱肉強食の　掟のみ！
Survival of the fittest to the very end!
一度名前が書かれてしまっては→
Once your name is written,
there is no longer any escape.
もはや逃れることなど
できるはずもない。
何が起ころうとも
やり通すしかないのだ！
You have no choice but to
try and get through it!
さもないと…。
And if you do not...
おいおい　男鹿
あのヒルダさんが→
Hey hey, Oga... Our Hilda-san
is acting really scared!
こんだけビビってんだぞ
ヤバすぎるだろ。
This is way too dangerous!
ましてや　大魔王様が直々に
送ってよこされた宿題だ。
Not to mention this is homework handed down
directly from the Great Demon Lord himself!
もし　万が一にも　不備があれば→
If, by some chance he were dissatisfied,
大魔王様がお怒りになり
あんな事や　そんな事が…。
his anger would be truly great!
He would this... And he would that...!
（大魔王）ん～！怒ったよ～！！
アイ～ッ！
I'm mad!
ここは何があっても
宿題を無事かたづけ→
We have to complete the
homework no matter what!
大魔王様からお褒めの言葉を
いただくのだ！
We have to obtain the Great
Demon Lord's words of praise!
よいな　愚民ども！貴様らの
乏しい知恵を振り絞って→
Understand, plebeians?
You will squeeze you meager knowledge out of
your heads and help the master with his homework!
坊っちゃまの
お手伝いをするのだ！
見事にやる気を削ぐ気合だな。
She's great at demotivation...
大魔王に会ったら　ぜったい殴る。
If I meet this Great Demon
Lord, I will so punch him.
わくわくノート？
OMG Notebook?
ノート１冊を絵でも文字でも
好きに埋めろと言う→
Each page of the notebook must be filled
with a drawing or letters as you see fit.
出題者側の手抜きかつ
創造性の欠如が見られる→
It's popular homework lately that
reflects the lack of preparation
昨今流行の宿題だな。素晴らしい。
ヒルダさん…。
and creativity of the homework giver.
Wonderful!
Hilda-san...
早い話が　全部のページに何か
書きゃいいんだろ？なら楽勝だ。
So basically we just need to
write something on each page?
Then that's a cinch.
よ～し　ベル坊
好きなものを　好きなだけ書け！
Okay, Baby Beel! Write whatever you like!
ダ～ブ！アイ。
アイアイ～イ～…。
≪ぼえっ≫
な　なんだこりゃ？
こ　これは…猫だ！
W-What's this?
It's... a cat!
まあ　なんてかわいらしい猫
さすが坊っちゃま→
My, what a cute cat! Impressive, Master!
絵がお上手でいらっしゃる。
ウソつけ！これのどこが猫だ！
You are so good at drawing!
You lie! How exactly is that a cat?
猫ですよね　坊っちゃま？
It's a cat! Yes, master?
アイ！
ええ！？
坊ちゃまが　猫だとおしゃって
いるのだから　猫だ！
Master said it is a cat, so it is a cat!
ウッ！はいはい　猫ですね～。
Right-right... A cat, of course.
（猫的な生物）ぼえ～！
うわぁ！取って　これ　取って！
古市殿…。
Get it off! I said get it off!
Furuichi-dono?
ぼっへ～ん…。
ふむ　なるほど
このノートに描いたものは→
I see. It seems like anything drawn
in this notebook gains actual form.
もれなく立体化されるらしい。
さすが沸く沸くノート。
It is indeed an OMG Notebook!
血湧き肉踊る趣向だ！例えば…。
Something thrilling and new! For example...
ほ～ら　坊っちゃま　ミルクですよ。
ダ～ブ！
Here, master! It's milk!
ングング…ブワッ。
うん？
さすがに味までは描けなかったか。
It seems drawing the taste is beyond me.
ちょっと貸して！
こうして…と。
Let me try! Like this....
出てきて　イケメン。
イケメメ～ン！
Hot guy ("ike-men"), come out, come out!
かぁぁ～…。
イケ…メン…。
"I" "Ke" "Me" and "N"...
くうぅ～。これ　字でしょう。
These are letters!
さあ　ベル坊　好きなものを書け。
はいはいは～い！
Now, Baby Beel... Draw whatever you like!
Me, me, me!
一枚だけ　拙者に一枚だけ
書かせてござ候～！
Allow me to draw just
one mere page, dear sir!
お前　ロクなもん書かねえだろ。
You won't draw anything worth crap.
前回　僕を素敵な海物語から
連れ去ったのは誰だったけな。
And who was it that dragged me away from
my lovely beach adventure last episode?
今回　僕を素敵な高原物語から
連れ去ったのは誰かな～？
And who was it that dragged me away from
my lovely highlands adventure this episode?
たった
ノート１ページ分の夢くらい→
Can't you at least let
me use one little page?
見させてくれたって
いいんじゃない！
ウフ　ウフフ…。
The absolute worst.
最低だな。
ああ　最低だ。
The worst.
ダブ。
えっ？
You are truly horrible, yes...
本当に最低ですな。
お前も同じだろ！
You're no better!
ホワイ～？
Why?
ああ～　採集キットか。
A collection kit... Will something
like whatever that is, count?
その　なんじゃもんじゃで
いいんじゃねえか？
ほえ～。
猫だ。
あ～　はいはい。
かわいい猫ですねぇ。
It's a cat!
Oh yeah, right. A cute kitty cat.
ちなみに　魔界の猫は
身の丈およそ８メートル。
For your information, cats in the Demon World
are 8 meters tall and destroy an
entire village before breakfast.
朝飯前に村１つは軽く全滅させる。
それに比べたら
坊っちゃまの描かれた猫には→
The cat that the master drew unfortunately
lacks power in comparison.
惜しいかな　迫力が足りない。
これでは大魔王様に→
This surely won't impress
the Great Demon Lord.
感嘆していただくことはできまい。
ぼっへ。
もっと大きくて　強くて　珍しくて→
We must collect larger, stronger,
and rarer prey of greater variety!
バラエティーにとんだものを
採取せねば→
魔界の後継者たる
坊っちゃまの自由研究としては→
That creature is surely not enough to be
recognized as sufficient for the master,
認められないであろうな。
heir to the Demon World.
んなこと言ったって
ここは人間界だぞ。
Well, sure, but this is the Human World.
そんなのがいるとこなんて…
そうだなぁ→
Is there a place with things
like that? I mean...
大きくて…。
強くて。
Large...
Strong...
珍しくて。
バラエティーにとんだ…。
Rare...
And plenty of variety...
おお！あれがあったではないか！
We have that place, do we not?
あれ？
アイ？
That place?
ズズズ～…。
なんだよ　あれ？
What the heck is that?
It's that cat-like creature.
例の猫的な生き物だ。
It seems to have taken a
liking to the big guy's head.
どうも　おっさんの頭の上が
気に入ってるらしい。
ぼえ～…。
Why is it coming with us?
おい　何で連れてきたんだよ！
仕方ねえだろ　家に置いといて→
What else can I do? If my sister
sees it at home, then...
姉貴にでも見られたら
どうすんだよ。
Your sister? She'll be fine.
お前の姉ちゃんなら大丈夫だろう。
だから　それが怖えんだよ。→
That's why I'm scared!
If she asks to keep it as a pet, then...
ペットとして
飼うとか言いはじめたら…。
ぼえ～ええ～ん
ああ　たしかに　それはまずいな。
Yeah, that might be a problem.
We're here. This is the hunting grounds.
ついたぞ　ここが狩り場だ。
Hey, hey, hey!
おいおいおい！
何で夏休みだってのに→
Why do I have to go to school
during summer vacation?
わざわざ学校まで
来なきゃなんねえんだ！？
If you need a place that has a great variety
大きくて強くて珍しくて
バラエティーにとんだものを→
of large, strong, and rare
things, this is the only spot.
採集できる場所といえば
ここしかあるまい。
Why the hell are you coming to
school during summer break, huh?
≪てめぇ　なんだって夏休みに
学校なんか来てんだよ　ああ？≫
And so, why are you here?
≪そういうてめえは
何でいんだよ　ええ？≫
Because I was lonely at home, duh!
（不良）家にいると寂しいからに
きまってるだろ！ああ？
And maybe I missed you a little, huh?
（不良）俺も　お前にちょっと
会いたかったぞ　ええ？
That makes sense.
な　なるほど。
納得するな！
Don't swallow that explanation!
Now, capture them!
さあ　あれを捕えろ。
いや　捕えろたって…。
Capture them?
The wrath of the Great Demon
Lord is a fearsome thing indeed!
大魔王様の　お怒りは凄まじいぞ！
I'm afraid to even put it into words!
言葉にするのも　ああ　恐ろしい！
想像を絶する　あんな事や→
I can barely imagine it!
He would this... And he would that...!
そんな事やこんな事が…！あ～　わかったわかった！
I know already, sheesh!
ん？
あ？
アイー。
Master, over here.
坊っちゃま　こちらを。
（不良達）あひゃあひゃ。
ダブ！
お～　こりゃ簡単だ。
いいのか　これ。
It's pretty simple, actually.
Can we... do this?
Now, on to the next!
さあ　次に行くぞ！
（不良達）ひええ。
Good Ni...ce shot.
（下川）グッナイスショット。
Hey, did you hear?
（不良）おい　聞いたか！？
The rampaging Ogre's started hunting humans!
（不良）あばれオーガが人間狩り
はじめたらしいぞ。
うおおお！
（不良）見つかったら　やべえぞ！
If he finds you, you're in trouble!
（不良）うわっきた！
（不良）ぎゃあ！
Oh, we've collected quite a few.
おお！結構　集まったな。
But they're kind of, plain. We need
like a rare one like a "horned beetle".
でも　なんか地味だよな。
まだカブトムシクラスが
いないというか。
う～ん。
ウー。
ベル坊！ちょっと待ってろよ。
今ガツンと派手なヤツ…。
Baby Beel, wait here a bit.
I'm gonna go find us a real flashy...
お？
ウェ？
（神崎）おいおいおい　てめえ男鹿。
Hey, hey, hey, Oga!
ずいぶんと好き勝手
やってるみてえじゃねぇか。
You're sure doing whatever the
hell you want, aren't you?
Coming to school during summer break?
You sure have a lot of free time.
（姫川）夏休みなのに　わざわざ
学校にまで来て→
てめえも　ずいぶんヒマ…。
セミとゾウムシか。
ふむ　もう少しだな。
A cicada and a pillbug?
Needs a little more.
これだけ　いりゃ　十分だろうが。
Don't you think this is plenty?
せんえつながら男鹿殿　私ごときの意見ではございますが→
If you will pardon the interruption,
Oga-dono, in my opinion,
蝶的なものがあると
完璧かと存じます。
a butterfly will truly
complete the collection.
蝶？
はい　例えば　あのような。
Butterfly?
Yes. For example, like that.
おお！あれこそ　石矢魔に舞うたおやかな一匹の蝶！
That is indeed the butterfly which flutters
through the halls of Ishiyama... Queen Kunieda!
クイーン邦枝！
Ah, well. Guess I have to.
仕方ねえか。
Hey.
よお！
（邦枝）お　男鹿！？
Oga?
Sorry, but can I catch you for a bit?
わりぃんだけどよ　ちょっと
捕まってくんねぇか？
え！？つ　捕まる！？
What? C-Catch me?
《捕まる？捕まるって
どういうこと？》
Catch me? How?
《えっと逮捕とか　お縄…》
Like, capture me?
Rope? Trap?
《罠！恋の罠！？
フォーリンラブ的な？》
A love trap?!
Like, fall in love?!
ちょっ　わ　私　恋とか　まだ
あのっ　本当に→
Wait a...
I'm not ready for... love...
む　無理だから！
I just can't!
お　おい！
Hey!
Why? Why am I running?
《なぜ　なぜ逃げてしまう？》
《心とは裏腹なこの動き》
My heart screams out to run
in the opposite direction!
えい　えい。
えい！
えっ！
ハァハァハァ。
なかなか捕まんねえな。
ハァハァ…。
She's not so easy to catch.
男鹿殿　ここらへんの柱に蜜を
塗っておくのは　どうでしょう？
Oga-dono, how about slathering
honey on this pillar here?
うむ　その蜜に　しびれ薬でも
混ぜておけば良いのではないか？
Yes. And we should mix in
numbing drug with the honey.
Oh, that's it!
おお！それだ！
賛同するな～！って　うわ！
Don't approve of that!
W-What's this?
な　なんだ？これ！
アイ！
ぼ　坊っちゃま。
まさか　それは魔界朝顔の種！？
Master?
Are those the Demon morning-glory seeds?
うむ…双葉の形といい
成長速度といい→
With two leaves and a high growth rate,
they are definitely from those seeds, yes.
まず間違いありませんな。
なんだよ　それ。
What is it?
坊っちゃま…いつの間に　それを？
Master, when did you do that?
アウー。
Here we go!
((行くぞ～それ！))
((う～！))
((アイ？))
((アゥ！アゥ！えい！))
Demon morning-glory?
魔界朝顔！？聞くからに
やばそうな感じなんですけど！
It sounds dangerous just from the name!
あ～いえいえ　大丈夫です。
Oh, it's perfectly fine.
魔界朝顔だけなら
大したことありません。
A Demon morning-glory by itself
is nothing to worry about.
うむ…魔界朝顔の特徴といえば…。
Yes. Demon morning-glory's
distinguishing feature is...
（不良）うわっうわ～！
...the fact that they're carnivorous.
肉食なくらいだ。
ええええ！
（朝顔）アムアム…。
I think that's plenty a big problem.
十分　問題じゃねえかよ。
Really? As long as you feed them
enough, they are quite well behaved.
そうか？十分な栄養さえ与えて
いれば大人しいものだぞ。
Yes. Had I not seen a Demon noon-glory,
ですよねぇ　魔界昼顔とさえ
出会わなければ→
I would have thought Demon-World plants
were much like Human World plants.
人間界の植物と　ほとんど
変わりありません。
（朝顔）アムアム…。
Um, I'm not asking because
I care in particular,
えっと参考までに聞くんだけどよ。
魔界昼顔ってのは　どんなだ？
but what's a Demon noon-glory?
そうですねえ　魔界朝顔と比べると
昼顔は多少　小ぶりです。
That is a good question.
When you compare it to
the Demon morning-glory,
the noon-glory is somewhat smaller.
その分　機動力が高く
凶暴性も上ですね。
But it is faster and more
violent to compensate.
うむ　花の色は大体　薄いピンクで
人を食うと段々赤くなるな。
The flower's color is usually light pink,
and as they eat people, they
get deeper and deeper red.
Sometimes the seeds can accidentally get
switched for the Demon morning-glory kits.
まあ　時々間違って
魔界朝顔栽培セットに→
種が混入することもあるが→
こちらも昼顔だけなら
問題は　さしてない。
But if they are only noon-glory
seeds, there shouldn't be a problem.
Oh, I see... Then, that's probably
it, right? A Demon noon-glory...
そうか…じゃあ　たぶん　あれだな
魔界昼顔。
え？
何？
まさか！
What?
It can't be!
（校長）ほっほっほ！
（昼顔）アムアム…プワッ。
校長が食われたぞ。
くっそ～！俺達の校長を。
It ate the Principal!
No! Our Principal!
カタキ討ちじゃ～！
Let's get revenge!
（昼顔）ヒュヒュ！ングング…。
なんという美しい色。
What a beautiful color!
Um, you said that the morning-glories were
fine just as long as we didn't get a noon one...
なあ　さっきから朝顔だけなら
大丈夫とか→
昼顔と出会わなければとか
言ってるけどよ→
一緒になると　どうなるんだ？
What happens when they're mixed together?
うむ…魔界朝顔と魔界昼顔が
交配すると→
When a Demon morning-glory and a Demon
noon-glory pollinate each other...
It grows into a giant.
巨大化する。
（ウオオオ！）
さらに歩きます。
（ウオオオー！）
And it can walk.
さすが交配種　人間界など
ひとたまりもないであろうな。
As expected from cross-breeding... Nothing
can likely stop it here in the Human World.
Hey, hey, hey! What should we do?
おいおいおい！どうすんだよ！
って　おわっ　あぶね！
みんな捕まってんぞ！
It's capturing everyone!
（不良達）うわ～ああ～。
It probably will carry them to its
roost where it can slowly savor...
恐らく　ねぐらに運んで
あとで　じっくり…。
（ウオオオー！）
なんの番組だ～！
Delinquents vs "Morning and Noon"-Glory!
What kind of program is that?
くっ　めりこみパーンチ！
Burying Punch!
Kick!
キーック！
トーッ！
（グォォ！）
Damn... It's no use.
くっそ～！ダメか！
Hey, isn't there some way
to calm down this flower?
おい！なんか　この花を
大人しくさせるもんは　ねえのか！
True...
そうだな…。
There was some kind of support pole
in the Demon morning-glory set...
確か魔界朝顔栽培セットの
中に支柱が…あっ。
支柱　支柱…これか？違うな。
Pole, pole...
This? No, that's not it...
エッ！ハッ！ちょっと！
これ　どうなってんのよ！
Hey, what's going on here?
てめえのせいか！こら男鹿！
Is this your doing, Oga?
シャレになんねえぞ　おい！
This ain't cool at all, man!
Shut up and help search!
うるせえ！
いいから　お前らも探せ！
たぶん　なんか棒みてぇなヤツだ。
I'm looking for a stick, or something.
棒みたいなヤツって
え～と…これは？
A stick?
Uh, how about this?
それは魔界ハエ叩きだ。
ハエじゃないものも叩くがな。
That's a Demon fly-swatter.
It can also swat things other than flies.
ぐっ俺！？
あ　ごめんなさい。
Me?
Sorry about that.
キャー！
Why am I doing this for that bastard Oga?
なんで俺が男鹿の野郎なんかに…。
ん？これ違うか？
Is this it?
うむ…惜しいな。
それは魔界うましか棒だ。
Close. That's a Demon Tasty Stick.
Tasty Stick?
う　うましか棒？
うまいと言うまで強制的に
食べさせられる。
It'll force you to eat it
until you say, "Tasty".
うぐうぐうぐぐぐ！
う～！
あ～！
Give me a break here!
勘弁してくれよ～！
あっこれだろ？
This, right?
There's one of those? Unfortunately,
no. That is a Demon yam.
そうきたか…だが残念ながら
それは魔界長イモだ。
Yam?
長イモ…ってあの野菜の！？
You mean like the vegetable?
ああ　だが魔界長イモは…肉食だ。
Yes. But Demon yams... are carnivorous.
（グワー！）
うえ！どわ～！
ふざけんなよ！あああ！
Screw this!
結局ないんじゃねえのか？
Are you sure it's even in here?
Look carefully. It should be here.
ちゃんと探せ。あるはずだ。
（猫的な生き物）ぼえ～！
ぼえ！ぼえ～。
お　お前！
ぼえぼえ！
You!
Leave this to me!
ぼえぼえぼえっぼえぼえぼえ！
I cannot forget the debt I owe
for being given life in this world!
ダブ…。
I will show you a little
う～ぼえぼえぼえ。
of my pride!
ぼえ～！
（アム…プハー）
((ぼえ～))
ダーブー。
I shall never forgive the likes of you.
ダブ　アイー。
坊っちゃま！何という
風格に満ちたお姿！
Master, what a truly regal presence!
さすが大魔王様の後継者！
You are indeed the heir
of the Great Demon Lord!
ダーブーアイー！
I shall never forgive the likes of you.
キャ！
イ…イ…。
あ～泣くな泣くな！
Don't cry, don't cry! Baby Beel, real
men don't cry 'cause of a little pain!
ベル坊！男なら１回くらいで
あきらめるんじゃねえ！
大魔王の後継者の意地ってヤツを
見せてやろうぜ！
Show it the pride of the heir
of the Great Demon Lord!
イーダブ！
Monja Anger Punch!
もんじゃの怒りパーンチ！
（ドォォン！）
What? Why was I sleeping here?
なんだ？俺
なんでこんなとこで寝てんだ？
てめえ　なに俺の隣で
のんきに昼寝してんだよ。
What the hell are you
doing napping next to me?
Why am I here?
なんで私　こんな所で…。
What was with that giant morning-glory?
なんだったんだ？
あのでっかい朝顔は。
They said something about
a... Macao morning-glory?
なんかマカ…マカオ朝顔とか
言ってなかったか？
Macao must be pretty crazy if its
morning-glories are that big.
マカオすげ～な。あんな大きな
朝顔あんだな。
I'm totally gonna wallop
that Great Demon Lord...
ぜってえ　大魔王！殴る…。
お　おい男鹿！
Hey, Oga!
（寝息）
クー。
（大魔王）
たたた　うん！たた…→
I know the song in my head, damn it!
頭では　わかってんだけどな～！
恐れながら大魔王様。
Pardon the interruption, Great Demon Lord,
人間界のご子息より
宿題が戻ってきてございます。
but your son in the Human World
has sent back his homework.
あ？なんだっけ？これ！
宿題！？え～？出したっけな？
Huh? What's this? Homework?
Oh, did I send him that?
ん？出した？そう。
I did? Oh.
Then give him one of those "Prize for
Best Effort" things, or whatever.
じゃあ　あれだ
がんばったで賞とか　あげといて！
がん？あ…はあ…。
Right...
たたた　う～ん　たたた
うんたま～んじゅ。
なんで　ここだけリアルなんだよ。
Why is this the only realistic part?
ほ～ら　坊っちゃま。
良かったですね～。
Here you go, Master! Good for you!
ダーブ！
ああああ…！
A-A night-glory!
ゆ　夕顔！
（夕顔）ギョールァー！
The master is acting strange.
He's just got a summer cold, is all.
No, I think this is serious.
Look. The Zebul Spell is disappearing.
That's proof that the link between
you and the master is vanishing.
Seriously? Then does that mean
I'm finally free of Baby Beel?
On the next Beelzebub: I've
Quit Being the BoB Brawler!
Are you really okay with that?